<?xml version="1.0"?>
<data>
	<movie>
		<title>Star Wars</title>
		<summary>The Imperial Forces -- under orders from cruel Darth Vader (David Prowse) -- hold Princess Leia (Carrie Fisher) hostage,
		in their efforts to quell the rebellion against the Galactic Empire. Luke Skywalker (Mark Hamill) and Han Solo (Harrison Ford),
		captain of the Millennium Falcon, work together with the companionable droid duo R2-D2 (Kenny Baker) and C-3PO (Anthony Daniels)
		to rescue the beautiful princess, help the Rebel Alliance, and restore freedom and justice to the Galaxy.</summary>
		<poster>https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/en/8/87/StarWarsMoviePoster1977.jpg</poster>
		<trailer>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=9gvqpFbRKtQ</trailer>
		<cast>Mark Hamill, Harrison Ford, Carrie Fisher, Peter Cushing, Alec Guinness</cast>
		<released>May 25, 1977</released>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<title>Big Trouble in Little China</title>
		<summary>Jack Burton, a tough-talking, wisecracking truck driver whose hum-drum life on the road takes a sudden supernatural tailspin when
	    his best friend's fiancee is kidnapped.</summary>
		<poster>https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/en/7/76/Big_Trouble_in_Little_China_Film_Poster.jpg</poster>
		<trailer>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=592EiTD2Hgo</trailer>
		<cast>Kurt Russell, Kim Cattrall, Dennis Dun</cast>
		<released>July 2, 1986</released>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<title>Lord of the Rings</title>
		<summary>In a small village in the Shire a young Hobbit named Frodo (Elijah Wood) has been entrusted with an ancient Ring. Now he must embark
		on an epic quest to the Cracks of Doom in order to destroy it.</summary>
		<poster>https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/en/0/0c/The_Fellowship_Of_The_Ring.jpg</poster>
		<trailer>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=V75dMMIW2B4</trailer>
		<cast>Elijah Wood, Ian McKellen, Viggo Mortensen, Sean Astin, Liv Tyler, Sala Baker, Cate Blanchett, John Rhys-Davies, Billy Boyd, Dominic
		Monaghan, Orlando Bloom, Christopher Lee, Hugo Weaving, Sean Bean, Ian Holm, Andy Serkis</cast>
		<released>December 10, 2001</released>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<title>Pulp Fiction</title>
		<summary>Hit men, gangsters and robbers converge in Quentin Tarantino's violent tale of revenge. Stars John Travolta Samuel L. Jackson Bruce Willis and Uma Thurman.</summary>
		<poster>https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/en/8/82/Pulp_Fiction_cover.jpg</poster>
		<trailer>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=s7EdQ4FqbhY</trailer>
		<cast>John Travolta, Samuel L. Jackson, Uma Thurman, Harvey Keitel, Tim Roth, Amanda Plummer, Maria de Medeiros, Ving Rhames, Eric Stoltz,
		Rosanna Arquette, Christopher Walken, Bruce Willis</cast>
		<released>October 14, 1994</released>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<title>Wall-E</title>
		<summary>WALL-E, short for Waste Allocation Load Lifter Earth-class, is the last robot left on Earth. He spends his days tidying up the planet,
		one piece of garbage at a time. But during 700 years, WALL-E has developed a personality, and he's more than a little lonely. Then he spots
		EVE (Elissa Knight), a sleek and shapely probe sent back to Earth on a scanning mission. Smitten WALL-E embarks on his greatest adventure
		yet when he follows EVE across the galaxy.</summary>
		<poster>https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/en/c/c2/WALL-Eposter.jpg</poster>
		<trailer>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=5RcNwlq7JSw</trailer>
		<cast>Ben Burtt, Elissa Knight, Jeff Garlin, Fred Willard, John Ratzenberger, Kathy Najimy, Sigourney Weaver, MacInTalk</cast>
		<released>June 27, 2008</released>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<title>Fear and Loathing in Las Vegas</title>
		<summary>The basic synopsis revolves around journalist Raoul Duke (Hunter S. Thompson) and his attorney, Dr. Gonzo (Oscar Zeta Acosta), as they
		arrive in 1970s Las Vegas to report on the Mint 400 motorcycle race. However, they soon abandon their work and begin experimenting with
		a variety of recreational drugs, such as LSD, ether, cocaine, alcohol, mescaline, and cannabis. This leads to a series of bizarre hallucinogenic
		trips, during which they destroy hotel rooms, wreck cars, and have visions of anthropomorphic desert animals, all the while ruminating on the
		decline of culture in a city of insanity.</summary>
		<poster>https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/en/6/6f/FandlinLV.jpg</poster>
		<trailer>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=_d0hEzXrWT4</trailer>
		<cast>Johnny Depp, Benicio del Toro</cast>
		<released>May 22, 1998</released>
	</movie>
</data>
